<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>audio.ooo</title><link>https://audio.ooo/</link><description>Recent content on audio.ooo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://audio.ooo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>sounds, packs &amp; noise</title><link>https://audio.ooo/packs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://audio.ooo/packs/</guid><description>Dive into the zany world of our soundscapes and noise sample packs on Gumroad, where the mundane becomes extraordinary, and the silence gets delightfully noisy. Forget about music; we&amp;rsquo;re talking about the art of sound in its wildest form. Picture a canvas painted with the bustling hum of a city at dawn, the serene hush of a forest blanketed in snow, or the chaotic charm of a kitchen in full swing.</description></item><item><title>MIDI, Audio &amp; Productivity</title><link>https://audio.ooo/software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://audio.ooo/software/</guid><description>Hey there! Meet &amp;ldquo;CC PAL&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;X/Y PAL,&amp;rdquo; your new best friends in the music-making journey, ready to rock your world on iOS. Imagine having the power to control MIDI signals on your synths and software with just a few taps on your screen - that&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CC PAL&amp;rdquo; for you. It&amp;rsquo;s like having a magic wand to command your musical army. And then there&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;X/Y PAL,&amp;rdquo; which is like the cool cousin who brings the fun to the party with its slick X/Y pad, letting you tweak and twist your sounds in real-time.</description></item><item><title>Bla Bla</title><link>https://audio.ooo/blabla/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://audio.ooo/blabla/</guid><description>Embarking on the journey of music making and creative coding is akin to living in a house full of grey cats—charmingly unpredictable, often perplexing, but ultimately rewarding. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into this analogy a bit deeper, with the structured elegance of a well-composed symphony, highlighting the unique challenges and quirks of this creative process.
Act I: The Allure of the Grey Cat The initial allure of music making and creative coding is much like the appeal of grey cats.</description></item><item><title>thoughts</title><link>https://audio.ooo/thoughts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://audio.ooo/thoughts/</guid><description>In the vast universe of music production blogs, mine occupies a modest corner. It&amp;rsquo;s a personal space where I jot down thoughts on making music, primarily when time allows. My journey through sound is not marked by frequent updates or a large following, but by a quiet dedication to the craft.
I explore topics like crafting tunes with Ableton, designing patches with Max MSP, delving into the coding behind audio DSP, and the tactile joy of playing with synthesizers.</description></item></channel></rss>